Just past the hour I want to walk the
ladies but are. We are not the most beloved
unbent so bought not about
I will get them out by
a crook as sure as my name
is you not from quite so.
Good at your service Oh I am done we
declined it sure why now it's Kate.
What. Might actually.
Take that. Take. To
take it easy. With your
pick up in
a minute. They. Just
Needed out they get right on. It would be
to eat. Don't know get over the good with
this early. They are so you look very
pretty in the spaghetti is as good as new
what you. Were come about are very few
thousand plods it was
unavoidable wait a minute wait
a minute this would be great you
just through I respect that I am
a bit was somebody I had
a few too many myself. Why have
we got to clean up this mess.
When I. Get busy.
Doing. What you.
Have on my night absent about and I think
you think it's frightening that I don't
think she's actually if you don't with us
dying but you see if someone else started
to pick up the map is bad we mostly But one
thing we have to be the first to reach
can group to make preparations to depart
immediately I keep trying to remember to
curse he who touches the jewel first is due
to our own Jim day. We must secure the
services of three and when we get them
to do our bidding as we best have food
before we travel I already. Know
already had we want to tell you don't have
any more all we got left is rotten hot
dog crap I don't have to call don't
take rabbit OK I'm not. Going to.
That furnace oh Oh.
Boys are.
You only or you.
Yeah.
And to.
Get out. You know you figure the
way that you are now
a guy. Could
be. A game you want us.
Well.
You are getting. I don't know when
a company couldn't catch me out. Oh
but I'm not tired I'll just stand by you
we only get on hot if you talk us into
with.
Yeah I did. Do you.
Not any eight.
Thank you so much. For.
Me.
Who. Would like to live. Like you.
This just can't be.
Me It even forgot that much. Oh
you are the perpetrator of this
holiday eight. Hundred Thank you.
Keith.
There's a dog and cat just
tell me what a lot of alone
a lot of oh man. Oh. Oh
oh oh but these three they are the ones
the gift that you were going to write.
Come from and who came and. Tell you
how would you boys like to make
a thousand sheep play next to your convention
to see what we have to do there is
a diamond which. If you keep your friend
can I mean this man will lead us to the
treasure now pay strict
attention. You know me.
I've been so good you are late I got the
diamond you got the gate sign oh my gosh
you know I don't smoke. No
move. They did their murderous
cutthroat. One hundred girlie Diamond
a lot of parents he sure was
me and if I had. You know with
that diamond I couldn't quit my job with
the door wouldn't be all right oh they
spend it you can feel
me to tell me your only
a dollar man. Well and the doorman do.
You good when you get me by for
a bit of it now but I'm
going to tell you. There's
only one one hundred carats diamond and
it comes from. That's government property
right and if we return it we'll get
a big reward yeah maybe fifty thousand bucks
boy with that kind of money but you've
been the one mum apartment on Hollywood
maybe but that Amory smile was
a cut throat suppose you cut my throat.
Well you know now don't worry we'll be
disguised we'll find the shortest way
I'm here to study this map closely.
We start here at joint goal down
the insane river over the give
a damn to push over across.
To the stronghold of small.
Oh well both. Are very Don't panic
Oh yes they're really going to but.
Only. Because we have come on.
The run.
OK let's find
a diamond. And.
Every anywhere in the diamond.
That was a chance to get
a yes. Oh
Fan. Spirit that got the room you
guys give it to me list even
before you.
Went spirit command you
to stand on your head
a pound of cure failed to notice. What
.
Oh oh oh oh.
Oh oh. Oh. Oh.
oh. Oh Thank you Guy. Why.
Thank you you're welcome. Right.
Well at that.
But it.
Looks like you have a job.